Bruce Jackson and Diane Christian collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound Recordings
  - Sub-subseries 4: Newport Folk Festival, 1967
    - 279 / 67 55 / Sunday night I, July 16, 1967, AFC 2011/009: SR0279; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - George introduces Oscar Brand, Jean Ritchie and kids to sing the Star Spangled Banner, then long silence (tape noise)
      - George introduces Camp Creek Boys from Galax and Jim Rodney
      - Camp Creek Boys and Jim Rodney [or Rooney]
      - The Lost Indian - Camp Creek Boys and Jim Rodney [or Rooney]
      - Sweet Sunny Sal - Camp Creek Boys and Jim Rodney [or Rooney]; with Raymond Milton
      - Roll on Buddy - Camp Creek Boys and Jim Rodney [or Rooney]; Kevin Fonnisey [?] from Newport joins them, or already there and is just introduced
      - Benton's Dream - Camp Creek Boys and Jim Rodney [or Rooney]
      - Lonesome Road Blues - Camp Creek Boys and Jim Rodney [or Rooney]
      - George introduces Pete who introduces Norm Kennedy, Lou Killen, Bob Davenport
      - Keep Your Feet Still Geordie - Bob Davenport; others on chorus
      - The Harbor of Belinsle [?] - Norm Kennedy, Lou Killen, Bob Davenport
      - Tail Army Sink (title?) - Norm Kennedy
      - Ball of Yarn - Bob Davenport; others on chorus
      - Lou plays jigs on concertina, Norm p[?] upon
      - Mouth music - 19 Penny Bit, Irish Whiskey (Jefferson Jig), Blackthorn Stitch
    - 280 / 67 56 / Sunday night II, July 16, 1967, AFC 2011/009: SR0280; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Lou introduces Red Sullivan and Young Tradition
      - Go Lassie Go [Wild Mountain Thyme?] - Lou, Bob, Norm, Will [?]
      - George introduces Rosetta Tharpe
      - Didn't It Rain - Rosetta Tharpe (guitar)
      - Precious Lord ([?] spoken introduction) - Rosetta Tharpe (guitar)
      - Twelve Gates to the City - Rosetta Tharpe (guitar)
      - I Can't Sit Down - Rosetta Tharpe (guitar)
      - Rosetta introduces Katie Bell Nubin
      - Katie Bell Nubin talks on courting when a child
      - Rock Daniel - Katie Bell Nubin? Rosetta on piano
      - I Ain't Gonna Get Tangled Up in the World No More - Katie Bell Nubin
        Speed goes wrong at the end
      - Oh What a Wondrous Thing - Katie Bell Nubin and Rosetta Tharpe
        Speed problems with tape
    - 281 / 67 57 / Sunday night III, July 16, 1967, AFC 2011/009: SR0281; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      One tape box panel indicates this is tape I, and elsewhere indicates III.
      - Oscar introduces Buffy Sainte-Marie
      - Buffy Sainte-Marie
      - Little Wheel Spin and Spin - Buffy Sainte-Marie, with guitar
      - Piney Wood Hills - Buffy Sainte-Marie, with guitar
      - Rainbow Midst the Willows (?) [Rainbow 'Mid the Willows] - Buffy Sainte-Marie, with mouth bow
      - Cripple Creek - Buffy Sainte-Marie, with mouth bow
      - Welcome Immigrants [Welcome, Welcome Emigrante] - Buffy Sainte-Marie, with guitar
      - My Country Tis of Thy People You're Dying - Buffy Sainte-Marie, with guitar
      - The Seeds of Brotherhood - Buffy Sainte-Marie, with guitar
      - George: announces intermission, says folk music ain't dead
    - 282 / 67 58 / Sunday night V, July 16, 1967, AFC 2011/009: SR0282; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      On the tape box back, "IV" (tape IV) is scratched out, and "V" appears beneath it.
      - Viper - Kweskin Band
      - The Garden of Joy - Kweskin Band
      - Minglewood Blues ([?]) - Kweskin Band
      - Lavender Boat Stay - Kweskin Band; Fritz
      - Elephant Song - Kweskin Band
      - Borneo - Kweskin Band
      - I'm A Woman - Kweskin Band
      - Gee Baby Ain't I Good to You - Kweskin Band
    - 283 / 67 59 / Sunday night VI, July 16, 1967, AFC 2011/009: SR0283; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      One tape box panel indicates this is tape VIII, and elsewhere indicates VI.
      - Theo Bikel introduces Joan Baez
      - Be Not Too Hard (Nothing Is Given to Man) - Joan Baez
      - Che Una Grande Plato Verde ("There's a big green place") - Joan Baez
      - Farewell Angelina - Joan Baez
      - Little Darlin' - Joan Baez
      - Bordenso [?] /Our Lives - Joan Baez
      - "Where icicles hung the blossoms swing" [North] - Joan Baez
      - Calls Mimi out [her sister, Mimi Fariña]: song ends "Ah but I may as well try to catch the wind"
      - calls Judy out [Judy Collins]
        [?] - 2 minutes
      - "Now is the time for your loving dear" - Joan Baez, Judy Collins, Mimi Fariña
      - Children of Danbury (?) - Joan Baez, Judy Collins, Mimi Fariña
      - I Am A Poor Pilgrim - Joan
      - Oh Yeah - Joan Baez, Judy Collins, Mimi Fariña [?]
    - 284 / 67 60 / Sunday night VII, July 16, 1967, AFC 2011/009: SR0284; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Oh Yeah [conclusion] - Joan Baez
      - Blowin' in the Wind - Joan Baez
      - Those Three Are on My Mind - Pete Seeger
      - Big Muddy - Pete Seeger
      - Just Want to Ride My Motorcycle - Arlo Guthrie
      - Alice's Restaurant - Arlo Guthrie
    - 285 / 67 61 / Sunday night VIII, July 16, 1967, AFC 2011/009: SR0285; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      One tape box panel indicates this is tape VI, and elsewhere indicates VIII.
      - Alice's Restaurant (conclusion) - Arlo Guthrie
  - Sub-subseries 5: Newport Folk Festival, 1968
    - 325 / Wed July 24 / Children's Day #1, July 24, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0325; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 2 track, stereo; 7 in.
      Performances took place on the main stage.
      - Sourwood Mountain - Sam Hinton
      - Take This Hammer - Sam Hinton
      - T[?] but [?] - Bernice Reagon [Bernice Johnson Reagon]
      - [?] - Eric Von Schmidt
      - Sam Hinton introduces Rev. F.D. Kirkpatrick
    - 319 / Wed July 24 / Children's Day #2, July 24, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0319; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 2 track, stereo; 7 in.
      - Rev. Kirkpatrick (I'm Not [?] My Lord)
      - Mike Casey
      - Libba Cotten [Elizabeth Cotten]
      - Jim Kweskin tells program
    - 321 / Newport 1968 Wed July 24 / Children's Day #3, July 24, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0321; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 2 track, stereo; 7 in.
      The tape box back indicates this is the first half of the children's concert.
      - Jack Elliott
      - Jim Kweskin and group - second part of concert
    - 286 / 1 Wednesday 7-24 / Seeger / Doc Watson, July 24, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0286; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Wednesday afternoon
      - Pete Seeger
      - Square dancing
      - Wednesday evening
      - Doc Watson
    - 287 / #2 Wednesday Night / McDowell / Reagan / English, July 24, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0287; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Fred McDowell
      - Bernice Reagon [Bernice Johnson Reagon]
      - Logan English
    - 288 / #3 Wednesday Night / McDowell / Smith / Seeger / Kirk, July 24, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0288; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Fred McDowell
      - Dan Smith
      - Mike Seeger
      - Rev. Kirkpatrick
    - 290 / #4 Wednesday Night / Kirk / Von Schmidt / Kennedy / Heaney / Killen, July 24, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0289; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Rev. Kirkpatrick
      - Eric Von Schmidt
      - Joe Heaney, Lou Killen, Norman Kennedy
    - 290 / #5 Wednesday Night / Heaney / Kennedy / Killen / Young, July 24, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0290; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Joe Heaney
      - Lou Killen
      - Norman Kennedy
      - Ed Young
    - 291 / #6, July 26, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0291; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Onward Band - opening
      - Bernice Reagon [Bernice Johnson Reagon]
    - 292 / #7, July 26, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0292; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Pennywhistlers
      - Ed Young
    - 293 / #8 Newport Folk Festival 1968 Friday Evening Concert / Arlo Guthrie, July 26, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0293; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Swim and police songs - Arlo Guthrie
    - 294 / #9, July 26, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0294; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Arlo Guthrie
      - Ed Young
      - Elizabeth Cotton
    - 295 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #10, July 26, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0295; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Joan Baez
    - 296 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #11, July 26-27, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0296; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Saturday evening
      - Joan Baez
      - Finale jam
      - Sunday evening (opening)
      - country band
    - 297 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #12 Saturday night / McDowell / Hamilton / IV, July 27, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0297; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Fred McDowell
      - George Hamilton IV
    - 298 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #13 Saturday night / Stanley / Jack Elliott, July 27, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0298; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Ralph Stanley and the Clinch Mountain Boys
      - Jack Elliott
    - 299 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #14 Saturday night / BB King, July 27, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0299; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - B.B. King
    - 300 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #15 Saturday night / Charles River Valley Boys and Baez / Crow Dog, July 27, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0300; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Charles River Valley Boys, with Joan Baez
      - Indian dances - Crow Dog
    - 301 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #16 Saturday night / Threadgill / Acuff, July 27, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0301; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Ken Threadgill
      - Roy Acuff
    - 302 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #17 Saturday night / Acuff / Theo Bikel, July 27, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0302; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Roy Acuff (continued)
      - Theodore Bikel
    - 303 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #18 Saturday night / Big Brother and the Holding Company, July 27, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0303; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Big Brother and the Holding Company [with Janis Joplin]
    - 304 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #19 Sunday Religious, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0304; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Sunday morning service, reel 1
    - 305 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #20 Sunday Religious, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0305; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Sunday morning service, part 2
      - Rev. Kirkpatrick
    - 306 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #21 Sunday Relig. / Sunday Afternoon - Kirkpatrick, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0306; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Religious service (end)
      - Sunday afternoon (opening)
      - Rev. Kirkpatrick
    - 307 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #22 Sunday Afternoon / Kirk / Happy and Artie Traum / Obasawin, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0307; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Rev. Kirkpatrick (conclusion)
      - Indian Princess [Alanis Obomsawin]
      - Artie and Happy Traum
    - 308 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #23 Sunday Afternoon / Traum / Geynier, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0308; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Artie and Happy Traum
      - Sean Geynier
    - 309 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #24 Sunday Afternoon / Kaleidoscope, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0309; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - The Kaleidoscope [Kaleidoscope]
    - 310 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #25 Sunday Afternoon / Brand / Buckley / Young Tradition, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0310; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Oscar Brand
      - Tim Buckley
      - Young Tradition
    - 311 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #26 Sunday Afternoon / Young Tradition / Mahal / Hartford, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0311; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Young Tradition
      - John Hartford
      - Taj Mahal
    - 312 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #27 Sunday Afternoon / Eve / Mahal / Sam Hinton / Jean Ritchie / Doc Watson, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0312; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Sunday afternoon
      - Taj Mahal (conclusion)
      - Sunday evening (opening)
      - Sam Hinton
      - Jean Ritchie
      - Doc Watson
    - 313 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #28 Sunday Evening, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0313; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
    - 314 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #29 Sunday Evening, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0314; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - J.R. Wells
    - 315 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #30 Sunday Evening / Wells / Ian, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0315; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - J.R. Wells (conclusion)
      - Janis Ian
    - 316 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #31 Sunday Evening / Ian / Guthrie Trio, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0316; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Janis Ian (conclusion)
      - Tribute to Woody Guthrie (beginning)
    - 317 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #32 Guthrie Tribute / Sunday Evening, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0317; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Tribute to Woody Guthrie
    - 318 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #33 Guthrie Tribute / Sunday Evening / 7-28, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0318; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Tribute to Woody Guthrie
    - 320 / Newport Folk Festival 1968 #34 Woody Concert / - Conclusion Sunday Evening, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0320; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Tribute to Woody Guthrie (conclusion)
    - 323 / Newport 1968 July 28 / Sunday Religious Concert #1, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0323; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      The tape box back indicates this is concert #2, and a side panel indicates it is concert 1. See SR0697.
      - Homesick for Heaven - Doc Watson
      - Old Daniel Prayed - Doc Watson
      - More Love Somewhere - Mike Cooney
      - Jesus is the Only Mainline - Fred McDowell
      - Glory, Glory Hallelujah - Fred McDowell
      - Sweet Rivers of Redeeming Love - Jean Ritchie
    - Newport Folk Festival 1968 / Sunday / Religious, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0697; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      See SR0323.
      - Side 1
      - Homesick for Heaven - Doc Watson, Clint Howard, Fred Price
      - Old Daniel Prayed - Doc Watson, Clint Howard, Fred Price
      - Jesus is on the Main Line (returns) - Fred McDowell
      - Glory Hallelujah - Fred McDowell
      - [?] Cotton [?] - Jean Ritchie
      - Sweet Rivers of Redeeming Love - Jean Ritchie
      - Wondrous Love - Jean Ritchie with Sam Hinton
      - Peyote Songs - Henry Crow Dog, his son [Leonard Crow Dog], and nephew [Andrew Stewart?]
      - Side 2
      - Everybody's Got a Right to Live - Kirk
      - Assassination of the President - Eks 7296
      - See How They've Done My Lord [same as above]
      - Ballstown - Sacred Harp Singing
      - Edom (Pent) - Sacred Harp Singing
      - I'm On My Way - Mahalia Jackson
      - Wasn't That a Mighty Storm - Sin Killer Griffin and [?]
      - You Mother Heart Breakers - Rev. J.M. Gates and congregation
      - Roll Jordan Roll - Fisk Jubilee Quartet
      - Every Time I Feel the Spirit - Christian Tabernacle Church NY [Harlem Christian Tabernacle Church]
      - The White Dove - Gallaghers
      - Takin' Names - Fred G
    - 324 / Newport 1968 July 28 / Sunday Religious Concert #2, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0324; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      The tape box back indicates this is concert #3, and a side panel indicates it is concert 2.
      - Wonderous Love (shape note) - Jean Ritchie, Sam Hinton, and others
      - J. Strike - Henry Crow Dog and Leonard Crow Dog
      - [two unidentified songs] - Henry Crow Dog and Leonard Crow Dog
      - [unidentified] - Rev. F.D. Kirkpatrick
      - "Not Uneasy My Lord" - Rev. F.D. Kirkpatrick
      - A Right to Live - everyone
    - 322 / Newport 1968 July 28 / Sunday Religious Concert #3, July 28, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0322; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      The tape box back indicates this is concert 1, and a side panel indicates it is concert 3.
      - Ralph Stanley introduces Father Jim Myer
      - Father Myer's introduction
      - Dan Smith
      - Joshua Fit the Battle of Jericho - Bernice Reagon
      - Come By Here - Bernice Reagon, with others
      - Shouting on the Hills of Glory - Ralph Stanley
      - Going Up Home to Live in Green Pastures - Ralph Stanley
      - Do Lord Remember Me - Libba Cotten
      - Bye and Bye - Libba Cotton
      - Oh How I Love Jesus - Canaan [?] Gospel Singers
      - There's a Long [?] - Canaan [?] Gospel Singers
  - Sub-subseries 6: Newport field tapes
    - 363 / Newport Field Tape 1 / Pete Goodson (Tumbleton, Alabama) #1, April 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0363; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - I'm Leaving Here Running - Peter Goodson
        Learned from dad, John Goodson
      - John Henry - Peter Goodson
        Note about re-positioning the mic
      - Lightning Hopkins tune - Peter Goodson
      - Leaving Here, Sure Don't Want to Go - Peter Goodson
        "From Dad"
      - Break Dance piece: Stop Time Bu[?] - Peter Goodson
      - Black Eye Peas - Peter Goodson
        Learned from someone's singing - mention who
      - Ball and Chain - Peter Goodson
        Learned from someone's singing in Georgia
      - Baby, Please Don't Go - Peter Goodson
      - Such etc. Same As I - [?] - Peter Goodson
      - Leaving Here This Morning - Peter Goodson
        Original guitar tune
    - 364 / Newport Field Tape 2 / Pete Goodson #2, April 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0364; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Take Me Through - Pete Goodson and Essie Pearce
      - Working on the Building - Pete Goodson and Essie Pearce
      - I'm Leaving Here This Morning (take 1) - Pete Goodson and Essie Pearce
        Weak-off mic [?]
      - How I Got Over (take1 ruined) - Pete Goodson and Essie Pearce
        Learned from someone - can't remember
      - Black-Eye Peas - form buck-dance - Pete Goodson and Essie Pearce
        Form [sic] buck-dance
      - I'm Leaving Here But I Sure Don't Want to Go (Ashford) - Pete Goodson and Essie Pearce
      - This Little Light of Mine - Pete Goodson and Essie Pearce
      - Take Me to the Water - Pete Goodson and Essie Pearce
      - O.T. Religion [Old-Time Religion] - Pete Goodson and Essie Pearce
      - Run, Sinner, Run [Sinner Man?] - Pete Goodson and Essie Pearce
    - 365 / Newport Field Tape 3 / Pete Goodson #3, April 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0365; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Leaving Here Running
        Learned from father
      - I Don't Want Much
        See B. B. King record; put together from another local musician
      - C. C. Rider
        From record
      - Going Back to Georgia
        Terrific
      - I've Been Running
        Buck-dance
      - I'll Fly Away
        Free for all
      - Ball and Chain
      - B[?] and Girls
        [?] there
    - 366 / Newport Field Tape 4 / Ashford 1, April 22, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0366; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      "Ashford IV" appears on a side panel.
      - Hooping piece - Joe
        Learned from Dad) (Joe) - liked to "frolicky" it / they dancing [?] piece quick time
      - Get Up in the Log and Get the Squirrel Tail - Joe
      - Catfish - Willy (Bo)
      - Coal Black Mare - Willy (Bo)
      - Hobo Blues
      - Jack O' Diamonds
      - When the Saints - Jim Jones
      - Christ is Coming - Jim Jones
    - 367 / Newport Field Tape 5 / Ashford 2, undated, AFC 2011/009: SR0367; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      "Ashford V" and "James" appear on a side panel
      - Little Sally Walker
      - Green Apple Tree
      - Uncle Jesse
      - Little Pretty Shoe
      - I Lost My Handkerchief
      - Hokey-Pokey
      - Farmer in the Dell
      - Step Back Sally
      - We Are Glad to Meet
      - London Bridge
      - Shoe Fly
      - Are You Sleeping [Frère Jacques]
      - Good Morning, Merry Sunshine
      - Miss Mary
      - Rubber Dolly
      - [?]
      - Ice Cream Cone
      - Cinderella
      - Bride, Stove, Chicken Hoop
      - Rich Man, Poor Man
      - Do-Re-Mi
    - 368 / Newport Field Tape 6 / Ashford 3, undated, AFC 2011/009: SR0368; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      "Ashford VI" and "James" appear on a side panel
      - One Little Donkey Sitting in the Hay
      - Little Indians
      - One, Two, Buckle My Shoe
      - Get On Board, Little Children
      - Going 'Round the Mountain
      - Wh[?] chipmunk record
      - Skip to My Lou
      - Shortenin' Bread
      - Hit My Shoulder
      - Pizza, Pizza - Mighty Mo
      - Both Your Hands Belong to Me
      - Polly-Wolly-Doodle
      - Knick-Knack
      - Ants Go Marching
      - Wise Man Build His House Upon the P[?]
    - 369 / Newport Field Tape 7 / Ashford 4, April 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0369; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      "Ashford VII" appears on a side panel. See note for SR0366.
      - Rock Me, Baby - Willy Doss on Silvertone guitar
      - Catfish - Willy Doss on Silvertone guitar
      - I Had a Woman
        On harmonica
      - Somebody Called Me on the Telephone
        Has verses; harmonica solo
      - Standing At My Window - Willy and James Freeman
      - G[?]n With Your Head Out the Window - Bertha May Ashley and John Henry Ashley
      - I'm Here By Myself (Bell Done Tolled) - Bertha May Ashley and John Henry Ashley
      - Come On, Brother, Let's Go 'Round This Wall - Bertha May Ashley and John Henry Ashley
      - Lord I'm Down Here By Myself - Bertha May Ashley and John Henry Ashley
      - Have to Pray Hard to Get Along - Bertha (lead), J.H. (bass), James (guitar[?]), Rose Jackson, [?]
      - Just Go On and I'll Go With You - Bertha (lead), J.H. (bass), James (guitar[?]), Rose Jackson, [?]
    - 370 / Newport Field Tape 8 / Ashford 5, April 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0370; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      "Ashford VIII" appears on a side panel.
      - Just Go On and I'll Go With You - Bertha, J.H., and Rose
      - Just Like John - Bertha, J.H., and Rose
      - Time Is Winding Up (Be Moved) - Bertha, J.H., Rose, and James
      - When the World's On Fire - Jim Jones, with guitar
      - Matchbox Blues - Jim Jones, with guitar
      - Don't Ever Leave Me - James Freeman and Jim Jones
      - Mama Don't Tear My Clothes - Jim Jones
      - [?] - Jim Jones
      - Boogie Woogie - Willy
      - R.R. Blues - James Freeman and Willy Doss
      - Deep Blue Sea Blues - Willy
      - Story behind [?] song
    - 371 / Newport Field Tape 9 / Ashford 6, April 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0371; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      "Ashford IX" appears on a side panel. Further notes on the tape box back: John - 67 on August 5 Henry County / Bertha - 62 on 25 December 1963 Henry County, Alabama near [?]e [?] to Ashford in 47 - always sang in church [???] / Willy - 64 on March 28 born [?], Mississippi; raised in Cleveland, Mississippi. Started to play age 15-16 years. Howlin' Wolf and Willy played together. Moved to Ashford in 1953. From [?], 76.
      - Ain't That A Man - Willy
      - Sally Walker - Willy, harmonica solo
      - Children's game discussion - Bertha sings Sally Walker
      - You Won't Worry My Life Anymore - Willy (harmonica)
      - The Apple Tree Blues - Willy (harmonica)
      - Got My Eyes on You - Willy (with guitar)
      - He's Mine - How You Know - Bertha and John
      - Whole World In His Hand
      - I'll Be Waiting Up There
    - 372 / Newport Field Tape 10 / Ashford Sacred, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0372; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Jesus Is My Only Friend - Warren Tower [?] (lead), Rose, and John
      - [unidentified]
      - Wonder What's the Matter with the Church Today - T[?], John, Henry, Bertha, and Rose
      - Handwriting on the Wall
      - I Got One More River to Cross
      - Nobody But Me
      - Don't You Want to Go
    - 373 / Newport Field Tape 11 / Union Grove Church (1) / Easter, April 17, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0373; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.